SURBHI SATI

PROFILE

An adaptable and responsible professional seeking a mid-level position in an Investment Firm which will utilise my specialised operational and communication skills developed in a private equity fund.

Present a track record of +6 years of experience dedicated to the field of Fund Administration, Fund Accounting, ESG Matters, Fund Compliances, Investor Reporting & Support.

EXPERIENCE

MANAGER (FINANCE & CONTROL), RABO EQUITY ADVISORS, - MARCH 2015-MARCH 2017

Responsible for the end to end fund administration of the two private equity funds advised by the Company. Job involved maintaining relationships with the fund manager, outsourced service providers, coordinating the work flow at all levels and structure of the two funds being managed by the Company. Independently handled the fund accounting, tax, regulatory filings, compliances, generated quarterly reporting for the LPs.

In March 2016, I have been given the role of the business integrity and governance officer for the fund. Have worked out the plan for integrating environmental and business integrity considerations in the investment decision making process. Have performed checks and tests on the portfolio companies of the funds. Responsible for the ESG matters.

ASSISTANT MANAGER (FINANCE & CONTROL), RABO EQUITY ADVISORS, –
DECEMBER 2011-FEBRUARY 2015

Responsible for day to day accounting and generating reports for the Management, handled investor queries and build relationships with the various parties involved in the private equity fund structure. Liaise with the fund manger, vendors and the portfolio companies for the various administrative matters. Handled the compliances, book keeping, audit etc.. of the fund structure.

TRAINEE, RABO EQUITY ADVISORS, – DECEMBER 2010- DECEMBER 2011 Performed desktop research for the sectoral mapping of the investments. Written research reports/profiling on various companies for in-house use. Assisted in book keeping, compliances and vendor management.

EDUCATION

 Company Secretary, Institute of Company Secretaries of India (A statutory body under an act of Indian Parliament) - 2007- 2010

Queenstown, Singapore +65 98134133 <u>cssurbhisati@gmail.com</u>

- Accounting Degree-Bachelors of Commerce (Hons.), University of Delhi, India -2007-2010
- Higher School Certificate (12th Standard of School education), from the Lady Irwin Sr. Sec. School, New Delhi, India) 2006-07